

## PHILIP WONG

TEL 1.604.716.1893
EMAIL philip@pwongfolio.com

WEB www.pwongfolio.com ADDRESS 117 10000 Fisher Gate Richmond BC Canada V6X 3W8 Extensive knowledge and interests in both computational artifacts and cultural experiences that include a study of historical, social, aesthetic, and economic processes. Philip learns and thinks both creatively and critically about the social and political world to expand his experience as a designer.

## EXPERIENCE

Designer & Founder | UNIFINE CREATIVE | Jan 2009 – Present

A personal studio to help small to mid size companies in website UI design & developments as well as marketing materials such as brochures and business cards. My role in this studio requires a lot of project management and business administration to establish a good balance between clients and quality of the projects.

visit: www.UnifineCreative.com

Contracted Designer | LEAP CREATIVE GROUP Nov 2007 - Present

Working under the supervision of the Art Director, my role is to handle the entire project from initial concept design to execution. This design firm provides many opportunities in project management and planning prior to execution, and collaboration skills with clients and teammates.

visit: www.LeapCreative.com

Visual Content Developer | OCTOTHORPE SOFTWARE May 2006 – Present

My initial role was to establish an visual identity for Octothorpe Software including logo design and various visual elements to provide a consistent identity for the company. Later on, I participated in the UI design on several software applications and websites with the developers to enhance the overall userability for users.

visit: www.OctothorpeSoftware.com

## EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts | SFU SCHOOL OF INTERACTIVE ARTS & TECHNOLOGY Sept 2003 - Oct 2007

Interdisciplinary approach to education and emphasis on teamwork to gain experience and knowledge in multiple research areas while learning from their talented peers. My technical strength lies on communication design, front end web development (HTML/CSS/JQuery) and an understanding in Wordpress Platform (PHP, Mysql).

## REFERENCE

Gavin Chow | ART DIRECTOR, Leap Creative Group gavin@leapcreative.com

Peter Tingling | PRESIDENT & FOUNDER, Octothorpe Software ptingling@octothorpesoftware.com

Vincent Wong | PROJECT LEAD, SFU Centrocity Project vincent@rfproductions.ca